Scott A. Anderson

12139 S Andrew View Circle, Draper, Utah 84020 Phone: (801) 703-6581 E-mail: scott.anderson.ut@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY

During my many years of customer service I have been able to develop many skills. These included working with people, keeping my work area clean and organized. I enjoyed the challenge to set up displays in the store to express a pleasant atmosphere for customers. This in turn increased sales throughout the year on a regular basis. As a manager I was given the responsibility to oversee the departments in forecasting the needs of how much product was needed. I was given the responsibility to be the store manager on the weekends. This included closing the store, balancing the tills and securing the money in the company safe. I'm a team player, proactive and get along well with my co-workers and those in other departments. I'm a loyal employee and will promote my company whenever possible.

EXPERIENCE

PREMIUM RETAIL SERVICES, Salt Lake City, Utah

Merchandising Representative specializing in Google products

2015 to 2017

Responsibilities included ensuring displays located within the store were fully functioning. This required on site troubleshooting and repairs if needed. This also required me to work with store management and associates in making sure inventory was available at all display locations. Other responsibilities included scheduling and making my store visits in a timely manner. Cleaning and maintaining displays are a key component of this Job. That included making sure the display was properly cleaned and had the relevant product specs and PoP set on the display.

MEDWAY MEDICAL, Salt Lake City, Utah

Senior Technician 2014 to Present

Responsibilities included learning and how to set up a wide range of Medical equipment for Patients on Hospice Care. These included hospital beds, Oxygen Tanks and Concentrators. I was responsible for delivering whatever equipment was ordered to the patients house or facility in a timely manner. Customer service was a key component to handling some very delicate situations in these families lives.

Frozen Food Manager

2009 to 2014

I Responsibilities included determining what and how much product is needed to order several times each week. I was responsible for maintaining all areas of the department. That included setting up displays for merchandising several products together. It was my responsibility to assist customers with special orders and direct them in finding products throughout the store. I maintained between a 5% -7% above margin of selling product and keeping inventory on hand for the past four years.

Dairy Manager

2006 to 2009

Responsibilities included ordering and rotating all new products daily to ensure that expired products were at a minimum. It was required to keep my department at a high level of cleanliness. I was also in charge of a quarterly inventory of all stock on hand. Inventory control was a high priority because this department is a high shrink area in the store. The Department of Health would audit my department. I received excellent scores on my reports regularly.

Courtesy Clerk/Trainer

2003 to 2006

Learned the techniques to bagging groceries and assisted customers in finding products throughout the store and taking delivering orders to their vehicles. I was able to get to know regular customers on a personal level. Responsibilities included store maintenance, cart collection and any jobs asked by the front end manager. I was able to train new courtesy clerks the skills required to bag customers orders and how to work with the customers.

EDUCATION

Riverton High School – Graduated in 2005 Salt Lake Community College, Salt Lake City, Utah. Major: Working towards a Business Management degree

Company-sponsored courses:

•Localization Training